<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.2.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2022-10-14T14:37:50-04:00</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">A Smolt in the Sea</title><subtitle>A personal blog.</subtitle><author><name>Esha Wang</name></author><entry><title type="html">Farm to Table to Mountain</title><link href="/newyork-2022-09-24/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Farm to Table to Mountain" /><published>2022-09-24T00:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2022-09-24T00:00:00-04:00</updated><id>/newyork-2022-09-24</id><content type="html" xml:base="/newyork-2022-09-24/">&lt;h2 id=&quot;september-24-2022&quot;&gt;September 24, 2022&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Kelvin made a brunch reservation at Blooming Hill Farm on Saturday, so he and Esha drove upstate for some delicious farm to table dining. The restaurant area was large and spacious, with tons of potted and hanging plants that Esha wanted to take home. They were seated at a small table by the window and knew immediately what they wanted to order. Kelvin got the Wagyu farm burger with cheddar, pickled onions, and garlic aioli, and he and Esha shared the Tomato Bomb pizza with tomato confit and scamorza cheese and the root veggie hash brown. Everything was made super fresh - Kelvin especially enjoyed the rareness of the beef patty, and Esha loved the sour cream served with the hash brown.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/tSDwNwXoTpOL_hU49gTTJA?viewBox=703%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/cY1uXIUST4G0lphICV58LQ?viewBox=1249%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/8N6SIaBuR-uq-t2K5LxPow?viewBox=1249%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/w8Kr2FohSgugZQsF7P4xNg?viewBox=1249%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After “eating too much” again, they picked up a loaf of Balthazar sourdough and headed to the farmers market to peruse some fresh fruits and veggies. They got a nice haul of apples, mushrooms, carrots, and some cinnamon zucchini bread to boot.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Though Kelvin got ghosted on his plan to visit Afternoon Acres, he salvaged the afternoon by taking Esha to Bear Mountain instead. Walking by many happy families and doggos, they arrived at Hessian Lake, where Esha’s eyes were drawn to a paddleboat rental. She was initially wary of getting her new boots wet, but Kelvin convinced her to go for it. After getting their life vests and boat, they paddled out to the middle of the lake; Esha benefitted a bit from Kelvin’s recent max resistance cycling workouts as her legs got tired. There, they took a break and enjoyed the scenery and autumn breeze.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/8xqk_hqrQhWFfzZ82KJWqA?viewBox=1249%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/NoongC9BRv6EIyS8V8nAog?viewBox=1249%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/a5dTL76qS9KZwcl6BtPYjg?viewBox=1249%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When their time was up, they went by the lodge to get some drinks and snacks, though they had to wait behind a group of grown women buying copious amounts of stuffed animals for a gender reveal party…smh. They also stopped by a market stand, where Kelvin picked up two cans of yummy looking peach and cherry jam.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/48Yh-RdxR-y3qBkjXWD3qQ?viewBox=703%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Finally, they made the drive back home, and Esha made a new recipe for a delicious vegan miso sesame udon with pea sprouts and shiitake. They wrapped up the day watching Blossom watch TV from bed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/2k1_kTr9TdWJEjlFMDot3A?viewBox=1249%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/imq0bXbPTUaKN9YZUYIwiw?viewBox=1249%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/-kw-MLiHQBK-9XNC3g4WjA?viewBox=1249%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Esha Wang</name></author><category term="life" /><summary type="html">September 24, 2022</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Shokugeki no Kesha: The Sixth Plate</title><link href="/shokugeki-2022-08-14/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Shokugeki no Kesha: The Sixth Plate" /><published>2022-08-14T00:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2022-08-14T00:00:00-04:00</updated><id>/shokugeki-2022-08-14</id><content type="html" xml:base="/shokugeki-2022-08-14/">&lt;h2 id=&quot;august-14-2022&quot;&gt;August 14, 2022&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Esha and Kelvin’s sixth(?)(!) anniversary cook-off competition came a week late since Esha was supposed to visit Chicago; her flight there was canceled but they stayed in and stress-ate instead. Wait, that wasn’t that different from competition day. Anyway…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As usual, each person prepared a main dish, and Esha chose a dessert while Kelvin made the appetizer. This year, they introduced a scoring system so that the winner would be official(ish)! They would rate each dish out of 10 in categories of difficulty, presentation, and execution/taste, with the last category worth double for a total achievable score of 40.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The morning started bright and early with Esha preparing bread dough while Kelvin made a shopping trip to Costco for the freshest ingredients. It was a good thing that Esha started early, since the recipe she used had an incorrect conversion that caused her dough to be too hard and un-kneadable. The second time around she used more of her own judgment and it turned out much better. As Esha continued with the difficult baking work, Kelvin was first to prepare and present his appetizer - burrata salad with arugula, roasted cherry tomatoes, and pine nuts, served with toasted ciabatta topped with basil and cilantro. While Esha found the taste of the dish delightful, especially the tomatoes seasoned with vinaigrette, olive oil, and black pepper, Kelvin thought he could have done a better job with the plating and reduced the amount of liquid at the bottom of the salad. Score: 3.5 difficulty, 3.0 presentation, 7.5 execution = 21.5 points.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/rvNZSP1AR1CKKSI9lrhIYQ?viewBox=1249%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Esha’s main dish was a novel Hainanese chick’n, made of frozen tofu wrapped in tofu skin. The chick’n was cooked in green onion, ginger, and (real) chicken broth, slightly invalidating the vegan aspect but making it delicious, and served with garlic pulao, sliced cucumbers, sweet soy sauce, and a fried garlic ginger sauce. Esha’s care in the presentation of the dish shone through, and the immaculate combination of complex flavors and textures made this Kelvin’s favorite of the competition. Score: 6.0 difficulty, 9.0 presentation, 8.5 execution = 32 points.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/duOr7bu1R2GhX4xsobbVTQ?viewBox=1249%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Next up was this year’s most expensive dish, Kelvin’s $80 king crab legs, injected and cooked with garlic butter sauce and topped with fresh parsley. Kelvin bought a meat injector just for the occasion and had a lot of fun poking the joints to infuse the legs with buttery goodness. The meat was so voluminous and fresh and incredibly satisfying to dig out to eat. Just the sight of it made Esha drool; still, the dish itself was not terribly difficult to make, and Kelvin’s wallet was mostly responsible for the taste. Score: 4.5 difficulty, 5.0 presentation, 9.0 execution = 27.5 points.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/6TR5LUzvRhOnpj4he6LHiw?viewBox=1249%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Finally, the culmination of an entire day’s worth of mixing, kneading, rolling, and baking - Esha’s very own version of the orange ricotta sfogliatelle, which the two of them had been craving since their trip to Italy. Though made every so slightly easier with the use of a KitchenAid pasta maker, it was still an arduous task rolling and coating the many individual layers of the semolina “log”. The filling was made by mixing semolina flour, ricotta cheese, and candied orange bits, which Kelvin stole many tastes of throughout the day of cooking. Unfortunately, as Kelvin was helping to take them out of the oven, somehow the heat of the baking pan transferred through the oven mitts to his hands, and he dropped the pastries on the floor. Esha had to stop what she was doing to run to the pharmacy for vaseline, as he suffered second-degree burns on his fingertips. Kelvin had to run his hands under the faucet for over half an hour and developed blisters in between layers of skin, and there was a prickling sensation for a couple of days - overall, a 0.0 experience which he would heavily not recommend. The sfogliatelle, on the other hand, though suffering a few broken pieces, were still delicious and impressive looking, and Esha and Kelvin thoroughly enjoyed making their way through them over the course of the week. Score: 9.0 difficulty, 7.0 presentation, 6.5 execution (9.0 for filling, 4.0 for pastries) = 29.0 points.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/FhDXSUbpQfqh_nL_JiFaaQ?viewBox=1249%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tallying up the scores, Esha was the clear winner of this year’s shokugeki, for handling the parallel preparation of two highly involved recipes and excelling over Kelvin at presentation. Kelvin suffered his loss graciously (his burns not so much), and was still able to make two very yummy dishes of his own. He’ll look for revenge next year, as well as buy a new set of oven mitts.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Esha Wang</name></author><category term="life" /><summary type="html">August 14, 2022</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Mangos, Memes &amp;amp; Musicals</title><link href="/newyork-2022-07-22/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Mangos, Memes &amp;amp; Musicals" /><published>2022-07-24T00:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2022-07-24T00:00:00-04:00</updated><id>/newyork-2022-07-22</id><content type="html" xml:base="/newyork-2022-07-22/">&lt;h2 id=&quot;july-22-2022---july-24-2022&quot;&gt;July 22, 2022 - July 24, 2022&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Esha wanted Mango Mango Dessert to celebrate the end of another work week, so she and Kelvin took the PATH to Hoboken on Friday evening. As they strolled down Washington St., they made a couple of short stops. First, they were drawn into Carlo’s Bakery by a sign advertising lobster tails, which they discovered are what sfogliatelle are called in the U.S. These were filled with a creamy custard rather than orange ricotta, but Kelvin and Esha still enjoyed one alongside a chocolate strawberry cheesecake.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/QApIHJ2pRSKuAUsDkmWrMw?viewBox=703%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Two blocks further, they grabbed a small dinner at Mamoun’s Falafel consisting of falafel, hummus, and baba ganoush. They made it across the street to Sephora before closing time, where Esha did a return while also planning out her regimen for Kelvin’s facial treatment (inspired by his mom’s bday gift). Finally, they arrived at Mango Mango where they shared a refreshing mango juice with watermelon and rice ball.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/cYvHf2fQRti5cLf0_Ue83Q?viewBox=703%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/IjYZWIsqRqaSK6IXAjTmzA?viewBox=703%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When they returned home, Esha persuaded Kelvin to accept his spa treatment while he lied on the couch. Thus, he got his first experience with Glow Recipe’s Watermelon Glow Hyaluronic Clay Pore-Tight Facial, Innisfree’s Green Tea Cleansing Foam, SKII’s Facial Treatment Essense, and Glow Recipe’s Watermelon Glow Ultra-Fine Mist. Though he couldn’t stop laughing at first, Kelvin eventually relaxed to the scent of honeycrisp apple candle, Esha’s superb neck massage, and Cateen’s piano concert playing in the background. With a glowing visage, he then fired up the stream to play the new game Stray, but his spotlight was quickly stolen by B&amp;amp;B #catswatchingstray (&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.twitch.tv/videos/1540110682&quot;&gt;https://www.twitch.tv/videos/1540110682&lt;/a&gt;).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/PZ2AMB66Ssiw2jjbM6ok5w?viewBox=703%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/Y9p1gBUmQ_qXRRbK7-zHAQ?viewBox=703%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/Qh2ly6B7RJSm4McsaVEhEg?viewBox=716%2C395&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On Saturday, after both working through the morning, Kelvin paid Esha back for the facial by dragging her with him to the gym (you’re welcome Nathan). They worked out for an hour, until Esha got noodle arms, then they made a trip to TJ’s. With their grocery shopping completed, Kelvin set to work trying out a new muhammara recipe they found while Esha prepped their homemade pizza. They happily devoured their meal as they watched the last season of Peaky Blinders, then Esha asked if Kelvin could make the My FFXIV Party meme for Team Jellicles. Kelvin pulled up some adventurer plates and attempted to copy them in detail, but both he and Esha found it to be a bit difficult. They temporarily gave up the notion after struggling to draw Garr and went to bed with some kitty cuddles.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/eNeepugEQYiCkPqmyPGB3Q?viewBox=1249%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/ArEe0vwoQJqNRnLBsDt3KQ?viewBox=703%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/TpKgg3l0T46mI3TsYOiWzQ?viewBox=1249%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/zHL-Tz99Tt2zHgErI3HwcQ?viewBox=703%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The next morning, Kelvin found some artistic inspiration and started again on the drawing with a simpler style. He quickly found his flow and soldiered through all eight portraits over the span of a few hours, as Esha provided supporting commentary and prepared lunch. Together, they filled out the quotes and descriptions of Team Jellicles, then shared the meme to Dream, laughing uncontrollably as their teammates witnessed their likenesses.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/Kk5MZ1gxRPSC66YIjng_IA?viewBox=937%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With that task finished, they set out for Broadway to finally see The Phantom of the Opera, which Kelvin had been waiting 14 years for. Their seats were in the rear orchestra at the Majestic Theatre, and from the start, the stage effects were flashy (literally) and incredible. The boat scene in particular was breathtaking, and the music throughout was so powerful and emotional. Esha didn’t know anything about the plot beforehand and found the ending quite sad, and Kelvin, who had seen the movie many times, was impressed how good the character getup and acting in the real musical were.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/gn920U0rSv2GVu5LAdu8KQ?viewBox=703%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/e5U84cuhQEOa40QIqt3akQ?viewBox=703%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/VnvVyh3GTCqMueLmuLFy-w?viewBox=1249%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Since the show started at 5pm, they walked over to dinner afterwards, continuing their vegan streak with Beyond Sushi. They ordered the gua bao, charred avocado maki roll, shiitake truffle dumplings, and nori taco sampler. Everything was super flavorful, especially the sampler of spicy jackfruit “crab”, sriracha “zalmon”, and yuzu infused “tuna”, which somehow all had the consistency of actual seafood.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/arvFZ1KCQnKGsVT-aA78zA?viewBox=703%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/x6yFQOsoRaSNxbkn3zwoAA?viewBox=703%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/4yZ7dusOT9y_TwG5yv3hKg?viewBox=1249%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/b4HK6EHCSFaAYzW5HA3t6g?viewBox=1249%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After dinner, Kelvin and Esha made a quick stop at NY Bakery &amp;amp; Desserts for some strawberry tres leches and white chocolate mousse cake, and a free cake pop to boot. They ended a packed and productive weekend relaxing back at home watching videos of Phantom and making up songs about B&amp;amp;B :)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/n8xhzYN1RqKYMHDS6tX88A?viewBox=703%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/sykN5CCbRASi1rblT3wvwQ?viewBox=703%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Esha Wang</name></author><category term="life" /><summary type="html">July 22, 2022 - July 24, 2022</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">E’s Birthday Weekend</title><link href="/newyork-2022-06-25/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="E’s Birthday Weekend" /><published>2022-06-26T00:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2022-06-26T00:00:00-04:00</updated><id>/newyork-2022-06-25</id><content type="html" xml:base="/newyork-2022-06-25/">&lt;h2 id=&quot;june-25-2022---june-26-2022&quot;&gt;June 25, 2022 - June 26, 2022&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Kelvin flew back from his onboarding in Austin the night before Esha’s 29th birthday. As he continued his homework of reading TGCF on the plane, he was inspired to draw her a birthday card on his tablet. His neighbor asked if he was an art student, which was flattering both to his drawing ability and age, both undeservedly so. However, Esha really loved the card and showed it to her MXTX-obsessed friend(s). The two of them then spent the night sitting together and tidying up the apartment, catching up after nearly a month apart.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/4WcfjRkFSLuygUtuNHW99Q?viewBox=625%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On the 25th, Esha took Kelvin(?) to KazuNori, a delicious and efficient (Kelvin’s favorite combination) handroll bar near Koreatown. They got there not quite at opening time, but still managed to beat the massive lunch crowd, which soon pushed the line out the door and down the block. Kelvin and Esha each enjoyed the full set menu, with Kelvin ordering the extra salmon hand roll by Esha’s demand since it was his first time there. The rolls were fresh and delicious and came out fast, with the toro being an obvious highlight followed by yellowtail (Esha’s new gateway into sashimi), and ending with a trifecta of shellfish rolls. At $24 for the 5-roll set (+$4 for the salmon) and tip included, Kelvin found KazuNori to be fantastic value and is super excited to go again.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/M52Upk7fQPqgyZ2HYnRRDA?viewBox=1249%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/SFBI-q9FR5aHex-bAaUKHg?viewBox=703%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/jwsOlOS6TZecKPVaNxEG_A?viewBox=1249%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/-ia_-y_vQAaIfr9SG4n7iA?viewBox=1249%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After lunch, Esha wanted a drink to beat the heat, so they stopped by Biao Sugar, which they had passed by many times before but never tried yet. Esha ordered a summer special peach oolong, though her standard option of 30% sugar left the drink a little too watery. Kelvin got an ube brown sugar boba milk with pudding, which was much more sufficient just from the name alone. They collected their drinks from the intimidating tiger’s mouth, then headed over to (the world’s largest) Macy’s Herald Square for some shopping. Esha enjoyed perusing the 8(!!) floors of clothes and shoes while Kelvin was tickled by the antique escalators. Eventually, they exited the department store and continued on their way to Times Square.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/fW0zpDI6TxWTHnF05doSDA?viewBox=1406%2C1874&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/FDWEynJ_QsKn4SqRekjHHw?viewBox=703%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/owYJ6xaJSJmq_ZLTfeaXMw?viewBox=703%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/qLIFpoE8QcOtCclHFl68Tg?viewBox=703%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Around 52nd Street, Esha’s eyes were drawn to a pistachio bombolone, and they made an impromptu stop at Angelina Bakery. Kelvin also bought an amaretto and tangerine gelato, which took them back to their recent trip to Italy. Finally, they walked over to Bibble &amp;amp; Sip, where Kelvin had ordered a whole cake version of Esha’s favorite dessert, the lychee berry piggy, from Gary the store owner. They easily collected the order and added a set of tea cakes (earl grey, matcha, and Thai tea flavored), a grapefruit honey Japanese panna cotta, and camellia green tea for good measure.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/1mVkpmZQRmS7APbjlKXJzQ?viewBox=703%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/mFps47csS72edMixYBndNg?viewBox=1249%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/Coz8e0XoQMqMAEgCMNZC5A?viewBox=1249%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/I2OB2487Qgm4UgHvKXE4pg?viewBox=1249%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Back in Jersey, they made a quick trip to Trader Joe’s for some cooking ingredients and a succulent, which they dubbed Bojo-Jojo. While Esha set up her new terrarium gift from Janet and Lindsay, Kelvin made chicken shawarma wraps with spinach and feta fries for dinner. They enjoyed the meal while catching up on episodes of Spy x Family and The Boys.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/y9WtRG_1SJuNpBYBBZej5g?viewBox=703%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/yHutP6BzSoWtMpOtcWp9fw?viewBox=703%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/7oR4DVQkRSmntybX8dn33Q?viewBox=1249%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The next day, both Kelvin and Esha did some work during the day, but they went out to Salt &amp;amp; Ginger for lunch, a new authentic Shanghai restaurant that came highly recommended by Boyu and Amy. They were temporarily embarrassed when the co-owner Kevin asked if they could use chopsticks since they ordered 100% in English, but that feeling was quickly forgotten once the food came out. The spread of pork hock, eggplant with string beans, and black bean popcorn chicken was perfectly cooked, and Kelvin and Esha relished in the satisfaction of finally having found a dependable source for Chinese cuisine in Jersey City. Coincidentally, after their first time trying Salt &amp;amp; Ginger, Boyu and Amy invited the two of them to join for dinner at a soft opening for their sister restaurant Red Feather NYC.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/L1LepT6yThCymu1IdaGHIg?viewBox=703%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/L0cq-LciTli8TRMJbuRJiQ?viewBox=1249%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Kelvin and Esha made their way over to Greenwich Village and barely got in, as the co-owner Jerry was having a busy and successful night so far. Boyu and Amy were eventually recognized, and they were seated in front of a very cool phoenix logo. The group ordered quite a few appetizers, including seaweed chips, tofu and black fungus, and fried spring rolls. But as the main courses started coming out, everyone was treated to a surprise game of FPS simulator starting from Washington Square Park. Between waves one and two of incoming hysterical NPCs, the party was invited into the kitchen for a behind-the-scenes look at the operation, impressively run by just three staff members (including the head chef who was previously sous chef at a Michelin star restaurant). After peace and order were finally restored, Kelvin, Esha, Boyu, and Amy continued their meal of shrimp udon, bulgogi steak, and roasted chicken, while conversing with Jerry and Kevin (who had come over from Salt &amp;amp; Ginger on his own) and marveling at the nerves of steel possessed by restaurant workers. At the end of the night, they were given a generous friends’ discount for their dinner, but they made sure to tip very well for the borrowing of defensive barriers and offensive kitchen tools.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/vVM45P0xSweQT8Axw1HzLw?viewBox=703%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/WKs1SihcSMCQGMzaLvDYoA?viewBox=1249%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/mMAjNKTiTBKLl2Le2fO-Xw?viewBox=703%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/v8LTaq2LR7uCOS7pzD-xCg?viewBox=703%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To end Esha’s birthday weekend on a lighter note, everyone made a final stop at Van Leeuwen’s to stock up on ice cream and try the new Big Face coffee affogato flavor. The caffeine was not needed to stay awake!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/2acgiEfdQiyjj3bBLsknpQ?viewBox=1249%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Esha Wang</name></author><category term="life" /><summary type="html">June 25, 2022 - June 26, 2022</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">E Visits Banff</title><link href="/banff-2022-05-11/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="E Visits Banff" /><published>2022-05-16T00:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2022-05-16T00:00:00-04:00</updated><id>/banff-2022-05-11</id><content type="html" xml:base="/banff-2022-05-11/">&lt;h2 id=&quot;may-11-2022---may-16-2022&quot;&gt;May 11, 2022 - May 16, 2022&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;E started her month long funemployment with a trip to Banff and to visit Alm and Petite who lived nearby. It was E’s first international trip since the pandemic started, and the flight was out of JFK, so E allocated plenty of time to get to the airport and to the gate. Luckily, there were no major issues! The view from the AirTrain was actually quite nice, despite it costing a hefty $8 each way.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/ECmBDy5CRnSFFZiug8ypHg?viewBox=1249%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;E read several chapters of TGCF and took a short nap, which made the flight go by rather quickly. A few hours later, E landed at Calgary airport, where she was greeted by Alm and Petite. Afterwards, we drove to Red Deer (the Texas of Canada, as they call it), which was about an hour and a half drive away. Even though E landed at around 9pm Alberta time, the sun had barely begun to set, and we got a beautiful view of the horizon on the way to Alm and Petite’s apartment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When we arrived at Red Deer, Alm and Petite warned E that Loki was a blabbermouth and mini Maeve was a feisty girl. E came prepared with Churu though. Loki instantly darted for the treats, while Maeve hesitated at first, but eventually gave in. That night, it seemed like both cats warmed up to E, since this is what she woke up to after losing the feeling in her legs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/7AFwEEurQ1m3L46fuGctoQ?viewBox=1249%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The next morning, we woke up early to drive through Banff and north all the way to the Columbia Icefields, where we got to see the Athabasca Glaciers. We got the 11am off-peak tickets, which, to get to the viewpoint, consisted of riding a bus with some legit looking wheels through a steep and unpaved path. While the view was gorgeous, the glaciers were barely visible and significantly smaller than they were ten years ago (according to K), and E inevitably thought about humankind’s impending doom due to global warming. At this point, the only hint of the glaciers was a slight blue tint in the valleys between the mountains, and one had to squint to be able to see them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/rsEVB3nUQ--unP634QSN8g?viewBox=703%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/FFc6F2voSWCUAC7biqBLzA?viewBox=1249%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/KV9t6KrjRbiJpo0OIgoshA?viewBox=1249%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Icefield Adventure also included tickets for the skywalk, which was a glass bridge overlooking part of the mountain range in Jasper. On the way, E took more photos and even saw a couple of mountain goats!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/4CI8fH5CSj6FokMx1GK74g?viewBox=703%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It turns out Alm and Petite were both afraid of heights (mostly Alm), and had to muster some courage to walk over the glass bridge. E asked if they had seen Squid Game, and it was probably a good thing that they hadn’t.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/sN_4ulfuTM2UdKV5vOh2Ag?viewBox=1249%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/Iuykf7obQcOzk80aNbQnzA?viewBox=1249%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Afterwards, we stopped by a gift shop where E tried on a kid-sized hat in the shape of a bear (why don’t they make these for adults?) and examined some dreamcatchers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/vO7xkb9HSj-9LBPyfIil0Q?viewBox=1249%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/ghbplv_GS_23to4UqhInPg?viewBox=703%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Food at the Icefield was overpriced and looked not particularly great, so we drove south instead to do some sightseeing. Unfortunately, Saskatchewan Crossing appeared to be completely frozen over, but we were able to do the short hike up to Sunwapta Falls.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/ray2miyLQ9-h7Z9LQqVciQ?viewBox=703%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On the way to the Airbnb, we went to Boston Pizza for dinner, which is also where Petite previously worked as a waitress. However, Boston isn’t exactly known for pizza and this was in Canmore of all places, so E’s intuition wasn’t wrong. We ended up getting 2-for-3 appetizers and a large pizza, which we did a pretty good job with, considering we hadn’t eaten the entire day!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/56HhGE4tT36IaAqlA1-wNA?viewBox=1142%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The next morning, we woke up before sunrise to get in some golden hour photos for Alm and Petite, but it ended up being overcast anyway, so it didn’t actually matter. However, E did get some nice shots of elk. We first stopped by Lake Louise, but as with everything else, it was completely frozen over. Emerald Lake was only frozen over on one side, and we observed some duck jealousy and drama on the other.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/rQV86KCKTRirtnOinfEl6Q?viewBox=1249%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/6YNFJniNRlGk0vHjcLrCGQ?viewBox=1249%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/nqVCXGDnS3a2Ljoj4D2J8Q?viewBox=1249%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Afterwards, we did a short but very slippery hike down Johnston Canyon, where there was a cave leading to a medium-sized waterfall. It was particularly crowded since University of Calgary students were apparently taking a field trip that day.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/exFrQiW7SSmGYUVe4g6Rfg?viewBox=703%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/FuU1fGDvRMmh4dTJYGlIxw?viewBox=703%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/D5wffgydR8yZZ_Nd15vqRg?viewBox=703%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/YqDgpZD2QTClX_fKPVGnyg?viewBox=703%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After our hike, we drove over to the Banff Upper Hot Spring to relax and recuperate our minimally mobile bodies. The hot spring itself actually looked more like a pool, and was crowded with people of all ages, including a teenage boy dressed in a bikini.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/xjS2-H_QTk-QmadM1pyp5Q?viewBox=703%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For lunch, we drove to downtown Banff, and E took Alm and Petite to their first ever “legit” ramen place. All things considered, it was actually pretty good by E’s standards. For sure better than Shitsengumi! We also stopped by a gift shop that sold Rocky Mountain air (for only 15CAD!!!) and a “Chicago-style” popcorn shop which was literally just a Garrett’s knockoff.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/4K0MVgaFQB-LIbxvq5hUJw?viewBox=703%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/bOPfNgHzSQabeQpnGumkog?viewBox=703%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/KeBpnV4zSCu2Y7oOpnME1g?viewBox=703%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Later that evening, we rode the Banff Gondola up what felt like one of the highest peaks in Banff. Since this was around sunset, the view was absolutely gorgeous. At first, E wasn’t sure the Banff Gondola was worth the cost, but this experience definitely made her reconsider.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/t3e-lrf1TgaQ5Riie494QQ?viewBox=1249%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/VqAGVw9aT-uTr4IIlSeGHw?viewBox=1249%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/NQHfwbS4TcSYOKiGR1j1fg?viewBox=1249%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/aPpBWHwNToaGmULHMbnRLQ?viewBox=1249%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/dW8R0KhkQ-muYLm7vKR8VQ?viewBox=1249%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/Ey9gmRVqQUm8briHQyrE9g?viewBox=1249%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The next day, we decided to sleep in for once. For lunch, we drove back to downtown Banff, and E took Alm and Petite to their first Cajun experience! E and Alm both ordered a gumbo and jambalaya mix, while Petite ordered just the jambalaya. E also got some fried green tomatoes to share.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/RrcLHP5mRjW8pcUlFVLq4Q?viewBox=703%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/vpw6hgv_QfSb5YZaLuWtqw?viewBox=1249%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The rest of the day was spent mostly in the car, stopping at various places for sightseeing. We stopped by Lake Minnewanka, where Alm tried to go for a swim and regretted it immediately.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/QcllHJVAQ6GyqDte8khJMA?viewBox=703%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/GP4hGKizROKkEnfHtUBgZA?viewBox=1249%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/PLEnFU1FRH6F9xH7_MWPkQ?viewBox=1249%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/bFGZ1YikRjq-28PHtzp5CQ?viewBox=1249%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;E’s favorite part of the day was Sundance Canyon trail, which was about 3 miles each way. The trail started off very flat, but rounded into a forest and then a canyon with a waterfall near the end. The backlight from the sun was perfect for portrait photography, so E snapped a few shots of Alm and Petite, including ones of them slapping each other.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/-6V7BjnqR36ec4TegIRpqQ?viewBox=703%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/VicdA8QISDm3CsETfMmUGQ?viewBox=703%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/hshu1uFCQkSgwAkqVy4NNQ?viewBox=703%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/m9AepXNBQ56BCW6bv0zgIQ?viewBox=1403%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/ZT06iiUpRuGBNJOOlgq8uA?viewBox=1403%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/DzoOzM_9TEett177dpdQsw?viewBox=1403%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The following day was E’s final full day in Canada, but since we needed to check out of the Airbnb in the morning and therefore lost access to the park pass (plus Alm and Petite were tired from yesterday’s strenuous hike), we decided to just drive back to Red Deer. We made a quick stop in Calgary for lunch, where E took Alm and Petite to their first actual JBBQ (not garlic potatoes) at Gyu-Kaku. E later found out that Calgary is apparently known for very good Taiwanese food, which E is resolved to try next time! For dinner, to save on costs, we went to the grocery store in Red Deer to buy some ingredients. E made some broccolini and her signature green onion pancake while Petite made chicken tenders. Though not exactly what E expected as a final meal, everything turned out to be quite delicious.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/7cgNIAcYQJCX8LH5sKqCbw?viewBox=703%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/UtPsr88zSRWgvbIJBeNt2A?viewBox=1249%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The next morning, E said goodbye to the kitties, and Alm and Petite drove E back to the airport. We said our goodbyes, and E encouraged them to visit NYC if they ever got a chance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/_PQq6fNLQT2DsI3diXvb7g?viewBox=703%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Esha Wang</name></author><category term="travel" /><summary type="html">May 11, 2022 - May 16, 2022</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">HaWhyI</title><link href="/hawaii-2022-05-09/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="HaWhyI" /><published>2022-05-15T00:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2022-05-15T00:00:00-04:00</updated><id>/hawaii-2022-05-09</id><content type="html" xml:base="/hawaii-2022-05-09/">&lt;h2 id=&quot;may-9-2022---may-15-2022&quot;&gt;May 9, 2022 - May 15, 2022&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Kelvin arrived in Kona after finishing book 2 of TGCF. Shir and Joelanda grabbed him from the airport where he was already suffering the blast of Hawaii summer humidity. Expecting lush greenery, they instead drove past lots and lots of lava rock on the way to Punalu’u Black Sand Beach. They found some napping sea turtles, tiny mollusks, and a crab or two (besides Joelanda). Joel picked up a wild coconut and began to crack it on the rocks, and a random lady told them they were bad and wrong. Regardless, the coconut was cracked, but then ants crawled out of it and Kelvin yeeted it into the ocean. Next, they drove to Hawaii Volcanoes National Park. They saw some steam vents and sulfur banks from a nice boardwalk (no leg burns ty) and walked around Kīlauea crater. After dinner at Thai Thai Bistro, they attempted to see the lava flow but were turned away due to too many visitors. Back at the Airbnb, Joel prepared some sapote, but Kelvin found it mostly tasteless and 3/10 texture, would not recommend.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/BqEfYe3USLWccFP37BbpAQ?viewBox=1249%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/2E1WqetYR2OeNr6zcZc7qQ?viewBox=1249%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/_gFTtTsmQw2SzarRkF6OfQ?viewBox=703%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/wZ12-8EAQua03abktzWRpA?viewBox=703%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/vIyCRmBtTQucody1e8IpHA?viewBox=703%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The next morning, Kelvin, Joel, and Shir (Amanda unfortunately had to work) got breakfast at The Coffee Shack, which was one of Kelvin’s favorite meals of the trip. He ordered an ono benedict, which lived up to its (Hawaiian, not English) name, and a lilikoi cheesecake. While the guys ate, they enjoyed a scenic view of a private farm over the ocean and saw avocado trees and a couple of geckos on the railing. Afterwards, they drove to the City of Refuge, better known as Pu’uhonoa O Honaunau, where Joel continued his search for an ant-less coconut as they toured the religious grounds, and Kelvin got a close up video of a cute gecko on a noni aka “stinky cheese” fruit. Throughout the historical park, they learned about Chief Ali’i, wearing a cheese, resting on lava…owns all these pools, how’s he stay cool? With canopies! They also watched a very dramatic movie about the sanctuary, learning the custom of throwing a spear at visiting chiefs before negotiations and all of the horrendous crimes deserving of capital punishment, like casting a shadow or co-ed eating. After finishing their walk around the City, the guys picked up Amanda and went to Da Poke Shack for lunch, which had rave reviews from Shirley and other friends. While it was certainly a unique take on poke, being much more sauce-y with various flavor styles, Kelvin found that it covered up the taste of the fish a bit too much and was hard to rate. During their meal, they watched outside as Hawaiian cyborgs climbed up some nearby palm trees and rained giant leaves upon them. With the full party in tow, they then drove to the Honua’ula Forest Reserve to hike the Makahi O’oma Trail. The hike started off with greeting a group of chickens led by the cutest black piglet. Despite being warned by multiple online reviews, the group got slightly lost, blaming the complete lack of signage, as they wandered slightly too long through the meandering forest of Jurassic-looking trees and ferns. Still unsure of what happened, they managed to spit themselves out far downhill from where they started, but the long trek back was #worth since they saw a rainbow eucalyptus that they wouldn’t have passed otherwise. After saying goodbye to the piglet again (over an hour later!), they went into downtown Kona for dinner and dessert. A Kava bar piqued Joel’s curiosity, and the group ordered some “squid” lau lau and kalua, along with taro leaf-wrapped butterfish, which were all quite enjoyable. They ultimately didn’t order any kava kava after witnessing the shopkeeper mixing it with his fingers while describing its soul-cleansing and mildly psychoactive properties. After watching the sunset over the ocean, they got some gelato (lilikoi and Mauka trail - Kona coffee, chocolate, and macadamia nut - for Kelvin), then turned in for the night.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/0vGKi9XOSXubsJkfyoOObg?viewBox=1249%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/LGkWVzm5Q9WcmtwVe2RizA?viewBox=703%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/6JjfMgI9RBGD6mMfsDaKow?viewBox=703%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/yMuAxmrBTpurWqlEssjZhA?viewBox=703%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/mCkRAzmFTF63hsLLdjhVYA?viewBox=703%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/3pCInc5IRyG6Am1hruYBTw?viewBox=703%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/I3ucLEDcQ2K53KRRh9-aeA?viewBox=1249%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/E1i8KXEnTyGsgWI6v53VrA?viewBox=703%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/0kqyiWrsQ5Cq8NZ7fq-CnA?viewBox=703%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/y-FdNlJ9Rumu4Ajki1Ormw?viewBox=1249%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On Wednesday, the guys drove two hours to the Hilo side of the island. On the way, they stopped by Pine Tree Café, where Kelvin made the pro move of subbing fried rice with Portuguese sausage in his loco moco, making his own Hilo style that was nearly as good as Leilani’s! They also stopped by a fruit stand and got a fresh cold coconut for ten bucks. The shopkeeper cut it up with a machete before serving the coconut with a straw, and it turned out to be very pleasant. There was actually a lot of water, taking all three of the guys to finish it, and it tasted very fresh and light, unlike coconut water from the store. The meat was cut out after they finished drinking, which was a bit slimy but yummy too. At Waipio Valley Lookout, the group got a nice view of a korok forest, then they moved on to Akaka Falls, where they did a small circle hike. Per the fruit stand’s recommendation, they went into town for a farmer’s market, where they were introduced to lots of interesting fruits - huge avocados, candy apple bananas, apple mangos, grape tree, and a sprouted coconut! The shopkeeper asked if the coconut was for planting or eating, then hacked it up for them as well. They found a nearby sink to wash it in, then munched on it while browsing the rest of the stands. This coconut had a crunchy texture and subtle taste, which contrasted greatly with the younger version. After paying for their haul of fruit, the guys continued on to lunch at Tetsumen, where Kelvin ordered a curry ramen and a shirokuma, expecting cute bear-shaped shaved ice, but was disappointed by a random mound instead. In the afternoon, they went to Hawaii Tropical Botanical Gardens. Kelvin got swarmed by bugs and ended up with eight bites, though luckily they didn’t itch as much as the ones received at Yosemite. In the garden, there were lots of pretty wild orchids, as well as some huge mango trees that threatened to KO bypassers. From there, the group went to Liliuokalani Park and Gardens, where they chased some nene’s, and Rainbow Falls, before driving back to Kona. They picked up Amanda for dinner at an izakaya, then Kelvin, Shir, and Amanda played The Crew while Joel prepared a fruit omakase. Grape tree was quite sweet and enjoyable (except the seed), but candy apple banana was Kelvin’s favorite. There was also solid watermelon, though the mangos they picked up weren’t ripe yet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/z7Vj9gezQiiwwaxE442JCQ?viewBox=703%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/jh6UEL2yT5ycHNKjUmCvuA?viewBox=703%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/AqQGNHbjQs6Z_HWT2BslgQ?viewBox=703%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/IEFm_5bKQ92lJMZtmluOZw?viewBox=1249%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/Dx8uzj7oQc-Mk4_8fJal4w?viewBox=703%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/2RejeXQYQG6pAdSSK1tOsQ?viewBox=703%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/2sWp2Cc1SWieZBJJOlYlCQ?viewBox=703%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/5NB6NTx-RpmFNuRYlBh2og?viewBox=703%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/aV4WwC50SnCn0brq9FpKNg?viewBox=703%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/gI0sCKwuSHCUtv7E3mLT3w?viewBox=703%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/6nTs7BDJSB2P8J0HVHwcGQ?viewBox=1249%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/zX9bUipwQIKGCUuENTBrGg?viewBox=703%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thursday started with more fruit in the morning, then the guys drove to Pololu Valley. They hiked down to the beach and skipped some rocks and found some large animal poops. In the town of Kohala, they browsed some local shops and a market with more interesting fruits such as eggfruit and chocolate sapote. Kelvin bought a vegan ice cream sandwich made of coconut gelato, mango, lilikoi, and pineapple. With more fruits in hand, they went back to the AirBnb to taste test - chocolate sapote had a nice jelly texture but not much taste 5/10, and star apple was quite good; Kelvin even liked the purple part that he wasn’t supposed to eat, 7/10. Amanda finished work early, and everyone went to Kenichi Bento for lunch, then picked up snacks to prepare for a sunset viewing atop Mauna Kea. They did a few small hikes along the mountain then chilled in the car munching on Maui onion chips and ume candy as the sun traveled under the horizon. A bit of stargazing later, they went back for their last night of rest on Kona.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/uI8vIDv4TZenoa8CBjnkYQ?viewBox=1249%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/dwpYv2zPSfeIn6W0W5z7ew?viewBox=1249%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/1ByOJNFsSvCZCk1uATSUJw?viewBox=703%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/MKEFa2CERF-se8ye-oo8LQ?viewBox=703%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/Fsf-6jSoS5OQw1qnqyLXyA?viewBox=1249%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/xWn6oY6XTYSFJCv560c94w?viewBox=1249%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/HHN0HzIgTKu8wfS3uURkcw?viewBox=1249%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/XHI0DTtGTOeSZ5LmfS-Lmg?viewBox=1249%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On Friday morning, the four flew to Honolulu, getting jian bing for lunch and stocking up on some more snacks before checking in. They tried to coordinate with Stevelyn to visit the Pearl Harbor Memorial but got NACKed. It was just as hot on this island, and Kelvin took a nap between exhibits, then the group rode the tour boat across the bay to the USS Arizona and glimpsed a sea turtle under the water. For dinner, they met up with Mario, Max, and Natalie at Mud Hen Water and ordered the tasting menu, which had some very interesting fusion takes like mapo rice cakes and chicken long rice croquettes. They walked along Ala Wai by the river for a while, then upon returning to their AirBnB, Kelvin had to catch a gecko in a cup to save Amanda.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/flrWX4AATN-rWfkd4wpDHw?viewBox=703%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/MwAFQDNbRa2Tn_4FGb52uA?viewBox=703%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Everyone got up early the next day to get to Koko Head Café, a very popular breakfast spot, at opening time. Kelvin got the cornflake french toast with millennium bacon and shared some chicken dumplings with chipotle aiole. The group then drove to Windward O’ahu/Nu’uanu Pali Lookout, which had a gorgeous view over the city and the surrounding natural landmarks. They went to Ho’omaluia Botanical Gardens (another one), then Rainbow Crack Seed for some novel candies and Got Grindz for musubi. Steven picked up Kelvin and Joel later in the day, and they visited Mama Okai’s house, where they had a delicious homemade lilikoi cheesecake and chatted for a while. Kelvin discovered Steven’s childhood drawings and secret artistic talent, while Joel considered buying the neighboring plot to tend the bordering fruit trees as they admired Mama Okai’s garden. For dinner, everyone met up again at The Pig and The Lady, where they basically ordered one of everything. Kelvin especially enjoyed the ahi tataki toast and the pho 75 dac biet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/YLU_QZDsRdac54p2Ye2U0g?viewBox=703%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/CF4M7FI-QP2Np8W0BksskA?viewBox=703%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/qVg4ooDCS8ar0l5bJ1Q6qA?viewBox=1249%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/RhIMYrbiRwSNSEz344wjXQ?viewBox=703%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/9QEtZxS4QyKTYnAJ6MYzxQ?viewBox=703%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Finally, the most important day arrived - the gang made a quick visit to the aquarium in the morning and early afternoon, then got ready for Seorim and Daniel’s wedding. The ceremony was on the terrace of the Halekulani Hotel, and though humid af, they managed to avoid the rain. The food was delicious, and everyone enjoyed the whole carved kalua pig. After many cute speeches and veiled threats, the party concluded with photoboothing and a fireworks display! #planned. Kelvin missed out on an interesting afterparty but had to rest before a 12-hour flight back to NJ and a subsequent flight to Italy! #travel #wanderlust #hawhyi.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/m4uskkUsQx-VMG8Z4_WHCg?viewBox=703%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/Hg5-FMYvSgSPKbK4jxo9BQ?viewBox=703%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/tnWUDugpR86tLzQT6hUQEQ?viewBox=1249%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/kl_DN2saQXqiBX_0brilJg?viewBox=703%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/irTYgobDRHSNggqJIRZp0w?viewBox=1249%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/WZQx0G7_ReepfyLYlz6coA?viewBox=1249%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/UVevxanrTtedgXhWSoIW9Q?viewBox=703%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/HLZM5pVPQIu-Xe27En96yg?viewBox=703%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/l-H1kAPIRnyf_4foIb8pEQ?viewBox=1249%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Esha Wang</name></author><category term="travel" /><summary type="html">May 9, 2022 - May 15, 2022</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">K in NorcAAAAAl</title><link href="/norcal-2022-04-29/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="K in NorcAAAAAl" /><published>2022-05-08T00:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2022-05-08T00:00:00-04:00</updated><id>/norcal-2022-04-29</id><content type="html" xml:base="/norcal-2022-04-29/">&lt;h2 id=&quot;april-29-2022---may-8-2022&quot;&gt;April 29, 2022 - May 8, 2022&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At the end of April, K left his job at Bell Labs and began a month and a half of funemployment. Leaving his lovely gf and kitties behind, K flew into SFO (no direct flights to SJC wtf), where he was picked up by Dad and Mom, who graciously packed a delicious homemade meal that K instantly wolfed down. The first few days in Norcal were spent pretty chill, with a walk around Sandy Wool Lake with Mom, Sizzling Lunch and Somi Somi with Shirley + Derek, learning Wu Bie on piano, and more home-cooking.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/k_SvXhvjS-GbFUeb0MgNAw?viewBox=703%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/xArUEON_Qum2lVAQx45KVg?viewBox=703%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/Rqfox7kYQamd2JTwpVq8Fg?viewBox=703%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/E0Fng2k5R-y0meTkM41ZfA?viewBox=703%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/xDjbPDHbSi-URpXDrKlSXQ?viewBox=703%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/ia_9q6SkS8iRgQG1-BC7-w?viewBox=703%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On Sunday after dropping Derek off at the airport for his trip to Taiwan, the Fang fam went on a day trip to Sausalito. We had some yummy crab salad and lobster roll by the water at The Trident, then walked around downtown buying some unique colorful truffles and pastry desserts. We did a short hike to the west of the peninsula, then drove back into SF to wander around Stow Lake. K had never been there before and actually found it very pretty, and there were lots of cute animals including baby ducklings, turtles, and fish. For dinner, Dad swung us by a popular dim sum shop in Chinatown, where we got three delicious pork+veggie buns and a bunch of shumai and hargow for only 12 bucks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/ANQw6_FLR6yxsz37OzZIkQ?viewBox=1249%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/NFyFjRfvQ2OagrNk1qCv4g?viewBox=703%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/XSkxjiROQYCVDZzyhIGmVg?viewBox=1249%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/GsJ-oEeXSCu5TUf3-u5oGA?viewBox=703%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/Eef0-52kTvSVeGImEU2uWQ?viewBox=1249%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/VAClqYGdR4-pZMiKwELTOA?viewBox=703%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/_63VSmQCQXOyRiN7iYNPPQ?viewBox=703%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/lnXXEsPNRIu559_o4UQ3Hg?viewBox=1249%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While Dad and Shirley worked during the week, K fulfilled his IT duties fixing Mom’s computer’s random black screens and put together a recording of Wu Bie for Meev for Mother’s Day (YouTube link &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8h-4Cb5ETf0&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;). K got to try everyone’s new favorite restaurant Chef Liu, which had tons of different skewers in a special house seasoning, and he also discovered that Xian Kitchen had an amazing spicy dumpling soup, though the noodles were a bit of a disappointment this time due to a recent change in head chef. For real Mom, K bought a chestnut cake and multiple breads at Sheng Kee. On one evening walk, we saw some more ducks and rabbits around Lake Cunningham as well.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/RSx-nx9aT5O-oTJsxNGVeA?viewBox=703%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/_zWbd82jRsuGwnky3sVkYQ?viewBox=703%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/YNCE7M41QzadUlJ0Xhlj7w?viewBox=703%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/PvsNPsydRPenGEtVkcCEdA?viewBox=703%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For the last weekend of K’s stay, the fam went to Yosemite together for the first time since K was in high school, though not much had changed apparently.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/12mrPtAqRPOvhSZIl7RwZg?viewBox=528%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The first day had absolutely beautiful weather, with fantastic cloud formations lining the sky in every picture we took. The water levels were also quite high throughout the park, and we stopped by the rolling Merced River and Bridalveil Falls, where K got quite a nice shower (though small compared to what was to come!). K’s favorite part of the day was finding his old meditation spot in the Yosemite Valley field and taking a nap alone in the grass with the picturesque Yosemite Falls in front of him. We stopped by El Capitan, Swinging Bridge, and a few more outlooks, and then we headed to our stay at Yosemite View Lodge. We were initially horrified to find that our room was a complete mess of beer cans and dirty sheets, but we managed to argue our way to an upgrade, putting our patio right on the river! We still had to pay for WiFi though…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/6z-Cf0ioSY6NCL_g6H8PSw?viewBox=1249%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/UOfS_7QERTi2939PuPSlAQ?viewBox=1249%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/Hiut-c93Qy6nBm2RlidNjQ?viewBox=703%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/QKOZzMNIT2KLPs9vlf-g7w?viewBox=703%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/bXPRIbr9SXKYz2H38p00oQ?viewBox=703%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/_hX9olNxRfGs1FLcbOzwqg?viewBox=1249%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/W7Eb7VD3TmqozJqsthlvZg?viewBox=1249%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The second day, we parked in Curry Village and hiked out to Mirror Lake. During lunch, K had a small panic attack when he learned about the Covid requirements for entering the U.S., and he spent a few hours trying to hunt down accurate info and come up with a plan for E’s upcoming trip to Banff. After An Arduously Articulated Argument And Affront, K was eventually calmed down by E over the phone, and he and Dad decided to try and speedrun the Mist Trail before sunset. The hike up Vernal Falls was a super pretty and super wet one, with multiple rainbows on the way to the top. When we arrived at the last 0.3 miles though, the nearly straight ascent up was a bit more difficult than anticipated, and K had to take a number of breaks. However, with the power of sausage bread, he pushed through, and we got to enjoy a unique view of the very edge of the falls. On the way back down, we tried to motivate a few other struggling hikers, though the lady carrying her corgi did not seem to need much help. Eventually, we made it back to the village with a roundtrip time of just over 2 hours.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/-E0nXkZtRnCes2CUFTbMSw?viewBox=1249%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/lCYEepeNTamxB2MsTPlqKg?viewBox=703%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On K’s last day in Yosemite and Norcal, we passed by Sentinel Beach and The Ahwahnee Hotel before driving back down to Milpitas. We had to make a stop to oversee a tenant move out in Stockton, which gave K a mild Covid scare, but then enjoyed a delicious dinner of crawfish, crabs, and garlic noodles at Claw Shack. K packed up and said his goodbyes to M&amp;amp;M and continued on to FuNemployment part 2.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/InY6UQdEQ7aKyIh8IF1e7w?viewBox=703%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Esha Wang</name></author><category term="travel" /><summary type="html">April 29, 2022 - May 8, 2022</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Phoebe and Leon’s Wedding</title><link href="/losangeles-2022-04-01/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Phoebe and Leon’s Wedding" /><published>2022-04-04T00:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2022-04-04T00:00:00-04:00</updated><id>/losangeles-2022-04-01</id><content type="html" xml:base="/losangeles-2022-04-01/">&lt;h2 id=&quot;april-1-2022---april-4-2022&quot;&gt;April 1, 2022 - April 4, 2022&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On Friday night, E and K took the long flight from the east coast to LAX. K mostly slept along the way, while E stayed up to study for an interview coming up the following week. When we finally landed, and following an unfortunate series of circumstances, such as the shuttle taking forever, getting the rental car line moving at a snail’s pace, and technical difficulties that delayed us leaving with the rental car, we arrived at Seorim and Daniel’s home at around 1:30am California time. By that time, E felt like a zombie, and promptly passed out and fell into a deep slumber.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The next morning, E had to wake up early for Phoebe’s bachelorette party. K offered to drop off E and Dohee at the party, so Dohee stopped by where we were staying first. The bachelorette party was located at a park in San Pedro, and after another one of E’s “where is my phone” incidents, E and Dohee successfully met up with Lydia and Johanna and settled on a location for the picnic and backdrop. Danielle and Vivian joined us soon after, who helped out with constructing the backdrop and blowing up NSFW balloons. Lydia taught E how to set up a charcuterie board, which ended up looking both colorful and delicious. All too soon, Phoebe arrived with Charlotte before we completed setting up, and in true Phoebe fashion, she asked how she could help out. The rest of us were very insistent that she just go take a walk, but we ended up just talking and catching up a bit, since it had been a while since Phoebe had seen some of us.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After setting up the picnic area, we all had a delicious meal consisting of cheese, crackers, Godiva, and champagne. Vivian told us about her brave little two year old, Danielle talked about work, New York, and some drama about one of her old friends, E talked about not wanting to move to Austin, while poor Charlotte had to be around suggestive balloons about her brother. Lydia planned a few games, such as guessing Leon’s answer to specific questions. For another one, we each wrote down our favorite memory with Phoebe, and she had to guess who wrote it. E’s was fairly obvious, since “where is my phone” incidents can easily be extended to “where is literally anything, including a borrowed bracelet” incidents. After that, it was time for Phoebe to open gifts! She got several pieces of lingerie, some workout clothes, and an Aesop gift set. E gifted a picture frame from MUJI, along with some of the engagement photos she edited and printed out. Afterwards, E set up a self timer on her DSLR, and we had everyone stand in front of the backdrop to take pictures. We started off with the bride-to-be with each of the girls doing silly poses and making jokes. E attempted her best to do what photographers are supposed to do best, which is make their subjects comfortable and get them talking, making for some of the best candid shots. Phoebe and Lydia make the cutest sister pair. We also got a shot with everyone at the end, and props to Vivian for the carry (literally).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/xh-6KwQySWStrP7sUALueQ?viewBox=1122%2C749&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/3v3evFNiSKCQw8aTEtSgmA?viewBox=1122%2C749&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/miEANdNWThyUCG54m4YrVQ?viewBox=1122%2C749&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/X3aUYkKMTIu43OwHHk-rUQ?viewBox=1122%2C749&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/DCRiRwZiQWe3zH_nvmutOA?viewBox=1122%2C749&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Since Phoebe and Lydia had a family dinner to attend in the evening, we only had about two hours to head over and enjoy a nearby Korean spa. E had never been to one before, but she tried to act cool about it, and thinks she pulled it off pretty well! Since we did not have too much time to spare, we just sat around and talked in the hot tubs, but next time, E definitely wants to get a full body scrub. E, Dohee, and Danielle had a nice talk about moving, career, and relationships, which was refreshing since E felt like we all share a similar outlook, despite not having kept in touch all that well recently. After the hot tub was starting to get a bit too steamy, we went to the food court area to order some lunch. E got a salmon teriyaki, which looked like the least carb option. Dohee and Danielle both ordered a cold soba noodle, which looked great as well. Phoebe and Lydia laughed and talked about their family dynamic, recalling stories of their parents being the textbook definition of loyalist, their uncle who really likes having meals with them, and Phoebe and Leon’s trip across Asia seeing both sides of the family and seeing all the sights.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Soon after, it was time to part ways. Phoebe dropped off E and Dohee and their hotel in Torrance (thanks Jonathan), which was located at a convenient location right across from the mall. Dohee needed to get some complexion products, and E was excited to offer her VIB Rouge discount. Dohee ended up getting a Rare Beauty concealer and E got the NEST Seville Orange perfume oil that she had been eyeing for a while. We also stopped by a Mitsuwa, where E bought some mochi donuts and Fugetsu-do. Dohee ordered a mozzarella dog from Oh K-Dog, which E had a bite of and was quite tasty. E also ordered the new Teaspoon guava drink called Guava Sunset, which is described as a fresh blended guava and pineapple marmalade with a splash of lemon juice. Probably one of E’s favorite drinks from Teaspoon thus far! We also stopped by a lululemon, which E found to be as overpriced as she originally thought. After our short mall excursion, we went back to the hotel to relax for the rest of the night. Dohee asked E if there was anything she wanted to watch on the TV, and E shamelessly took the opportunity to introduce her to Heaven Official’s Blessing on Netflix. Mama Maeve would be so proud. With a face mask and lip mask, E and Dohee watched all the way until the end of the ghost bridegroom arc before E was ready to pass out before the wedding tomorrow.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;E and Dohee woke up early to get ready for the big day, but after our morning routine of Starbucks, doing our makeup and hair, and changing into our bridesmaid dresses, we ended up having to rush to our Uber to get to the venue. Luckily, we still got there with plenty of time to spare before the dress rehearsal. When we arrived, we said hello to Leon and Phoebe’s dad, and all the bridesmaids hung out for a bit in the bridesmaids room while K and Andrew went on a little joy ride in the latter’s rental Porsche. The dress rehearsal itself was relatively straightforward. Despite it being LA, the morning air was brisk and slightly chilly. E was paired with one of Leon’s groomsmen, and also in classic E manner, did not make a point to remember his name or anything else about him. Afterwards, Phoebe, Lydia, and their mom arrived from their professional hair and makeup session. Phoebe changed into her chicken cutlets and wedding dress, and the photographer took a variety of cute and silly pictures, including nostril flaring, farts, and a recreation of a scene from The Ring. The photographer was quite receptive to all of Phoebe’s (and E’s) crazy ideas, and we all had a pretty good laugh about it. After eating some tasty hors d’oeuvres, the guests were all seated, and we were ready to start the ceremony. Lydia walked first, followed by Johanna and then E. When E walked to the front, she saw that poor Leon was already sobbing, his eyes beet red. Seeing all the guests in one spot, E observed that the wedding was actually fairly small. It gave off a very intimate and familial feeling, which E appreciated. After the bridesmaids and groomsmen were in place, the guests all stood as Phoebe and her parents walked down the aisle. The ceremony itself was rather short, officiated by none other than Phoebe’s dad. We all had a good laugh when he accidentally called Leon by Lydia’s husband’s name instead. Phoebe and Leon then exchanged vows, with Leon’s vow starting off with “I am not a smart man”, as all good speeches do. Jokes were made and tears were shed, but all too soon, the ceremony was over. E and Dohee helped decorate the wedding cake from the altar flower arrangement while Phoebe and Leon went to take some more pictures with their photographer. Afterwards, the bridal party gathered to prepare an entrance and a little dance before lunch. To E’s horror, she and her partner were to go first. E ended up flailing her arms and spinning in circles, but managed to make it to her seat without being too much of an embarrassment. Lunch consisted of salad, truffle mac and cheese, pizza, steak, and desserts, which were quite delicious. After our meal, people started to slowly gather in the middle for some midday drinking and dancing. One of the guests had a little boy who was killing it on the dance floor, and he was definitely living for the attention xD. At some point, Andrew let K borrow the keys to his rental Porsche, and E and K ended up going for a short ride around the area. Eventually the reception came to an end and it was time to part ways. E and K first dropped off Dohee at her friend’s place and then drove back to Seorim’s house where they took a much needed nap. Later that evening, Natalie came over and we got Thai food for takeout. The restaurant had a pork belly pad thai was particularly delicious. Over dinner, we talked about horror movies, bees, and Natalie’s driving awareness, almost all in the form of Seorim and Daniel’s bickering. Eventually E and K couldn’t take it anymore and food coma’d to sleep.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/zecxUNGVT923e7Wxc-8IlQ?viewBox=692%2C923&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/t65p5acfRJys2kJEZ64TrA?viewBox=692%2C923&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/b5TCx1KqTcGQpQzjVunmUw?viewBox=692%2C923&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/UKEPSM6qR4qciTLSxN18xw?viewBox=788%2C525&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On Monday, E and K set out for their old stomping grounds, the 626. We drove from Inglewood to Arcadia, which took a little under an hour, to get lunch at the long-awaited Dumpling House. The ordering was quick and ambitious, and we were soon greeted with a table spread of two orders of pork, shrimp, and chives dumplings, two pork rolls, a string bean with black bean sauce, and a cold pork belly in garlic chili oil. We belabored the secret behind making such delicious dumplings while thoroughly enjoying every bite, and still couldn’t figure out how the texture and pork flavor were done so perfectly. The side dishes of string bean and pork belly were also great in their own right, and we both found the cut of pork to be better than what we had at Szechuan Mountain House. Unfortunately, K pushed E a little too hard in finishing all the dumplings, so we took the pork rolls to go back home. Even then, E groaned and stumbled in pain all the way down the three blocks to Half &amp;amp; Half Tea Express. From Half &amp;amp; Half we ordered K’s default ice milk drink with all the toppings, a lavender milk tea for E, and an ice milk drink and normal milk tea for Seorim and Daniel. There was some confusion as to which drink was whose when we got them since they were unlabeled, but luckily K guessed the right ones. With boba in hand, we headed to Tech for a short walk down memory lane. We parked on San Pasqual and went down the Olive Walk, up by the Turtle Pond, and sat on the bridge in front of the library for a while. We noticed a lot of younger-than-usual students walking around and discovered that it happened to be Prefrosh Weekend for the class of 2025 &lt;em&gt;shudder&lt;/em&gt;. Continuing on, we passed by the Wedding Cake, Moore, Annenberg, Avery, and Sloan, and then turned up the street to see a new AWS quantum computing building that looked very swanky. After our short tour, we went back to Inglewood to drop off the boba orders and say goodbye to Seorim and Daniel, then we headed to a beer garden called Father’s Office to get dinner with Phoebe, Dohee, and Danielle and Andrew (and Cici!) before we flew out. E got carded for the first time in a while, but then we enjoyed a nice night of catching up on everyone’s careers and travels, and of course congratulating Phoebe on her wedding.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/-aw_QEerQhaLgW6Pz0XyrA?viewBox=1122%2C842&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/JHI1AIEMToSMwzIYolsDNQ?viewBox=1122%2C842&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Esha Wang</name></author><category term="travel" /><summary type="html">April 1, 2022 - April 4, 2022</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">New York Botanical Garden</title><link href="/newyork-2022-03-20/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="New York Botanical Garden" /><published>2022-03-20T00:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2022-03-20T00:00:00-04:00</updated><id>/newyork-2022-03-20</id><content type="html" xml:base="/newyork-2022-03-20/">&lt;h2 id=&quot;march-20-2022&quot;&gt;March 20, 2022&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;E + K went to the Bronx to visit the New York Botanical Garden and see The Orchid Show: Jeff Leatham’s Kaleidoscope. The morning drive was relatively easy as we crossed the George Washington Bridge for the first time. We started our visit walking through the Perennial Garden, which had several distinct “rooms” separated by yew hedges. They formed the forefront of the main attraction, the Haupt Conservatory. Stepping into the building, we were met with a sharp increase in humidity, turning E into an orchid, and the insta-worthy kaleidoscope art installment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/QM4D0pDESqGETUAncDtZaQ?viewBox=1122%2C749&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/uU750mvtS22YUfF66Z-mlw?viewBox=1122%2C749&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/PjwmEQhESNWPfrILx2UzxA?viewBox=1122%2C749&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Throughout the rest of the conservatory, there were orchids and other plants from all kinds of biomes. K liked the ones that resembled Spanish dresses, and E found the upside-down hanging orchids amusing. There were also vines of thin vanilla seed pods and micro orchid clusters that looked like viruses. Between the rainforest and desert biomes, we walked through a rainbow tunnel that reminded us of Mario Kart.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/mDehaWUdTHyYS_YLke0k8w?viewBox=692%2C923&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/IUnSXrgUTP2ytXKyIn3VVg?viewBox=692%2C923&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/rLIjh8d6RIylPak0dBhdnA?viewBox=692%2C923&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/qgnUowODRUmy3Nw5Leo3JA?viewBox=692%2C923&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/NpjvdY0STEC-RoneCLfwTQ?viewBox=692%2C923&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After doing our (first) round through the conservatory, we went to Hudson Garden Grill for a relaxing lunch. We managed to beat the large lunch crowd and get a seat at a two person high-top table. E asked K to pick a cocktail for her, and he unknowingly ordered the one with three alcoholic ingredients, starting the meal off with a bang. We got a sunchoke soup to share, which included caramelized apples and hazelnuts, then E ordered the Senat Farms chicken breast, which was rotisserie-level juicy with perfectly crispy skin, and K the braised lamb ragu with mushrooms. For dessert, we ordered a lemongrass panna cotta that had a delicious ginger-basil syrup.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/bhBn81tuRxif5UhswVuR-g?viewBox=1122%2C842&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/gkX4iznrQbeW6ncmURaJdg?viewBox=1122%2C842&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/3Wxakcn3QxaiwEcIxN6zEQ?viewBox=1122%2C842&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/ZbXbTEFRQI2pZlVM_SNBEQ?viewBox=1058%2C923&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After lunch, we headed over to the Mertz Library, which was surrounded by a Daffodil Valley beginning to bloom. We watched one particularly round squirrel sniff its way through the field as we hiked along the trail and into the Thain Family Forest. After a while we rounded back to the conservatory again to sit in on an orchid care class, where we learned about epiphytic versus terrestrial plants and received some tips on improving humidity conditions for Buttercup back home. We were also able to help another cat + orchid owner to prevent teeth marks in their leaves!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/fN3xVSAfROuAuBuZk3YjFA?viewBox=692%2C923&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/sa8AdVt2SXmcrlnmrjIyQw?viewBox=692%2C923&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/RjgQgxOfTjOaSVYjPLtoUg?viewBox=692%2C923&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For the rest of our afternoon, we walked along the tram path, sightseeing the reflecting pool with Rolex clock, Chilton Azalea Garden, Goldman Stone Mill, Edible Academy, and Magnolia Collection. We tried to catch a ride back to the main entrance but were passed by full trams, so we rewarded ourselves at the end with hot chocolate and a yuzu soda from the Pine Tree Cafe. We also stopped by the NYBG shop, where E happily procured a flowery hand cream and card for P’s upcoming wedding. K then got the true New York driving experience, taking double the time to get back home, while E took a nap.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Esha Wang</name></author><category term="life" /><summary type="html">March 20, 2022</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Legendary Mutton Chop</title><link href="/newyork-2022-01-13/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Legendary Mutton Chop" /><published>2022-01-13T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2022-01-13T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>/newyork-2022-01-13</id><content type="html" xml:base="/newyork-2022-01-13/">&lt;h2 id=&quot;january-13-2022&quot;&gt;January 13, 2022&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Since K made the brilliant decision to get the both of us fake ‘rona on his birthday, E had to reschedule our reservation at Keen’s Steakhouse to Thursday night. Just two blocks from the 33rd Street PATH station, it was a quick trip on a chilly day. The restaurant decor was very interesting, with all the staff in black-tie and the walls adorned with photos and drawings of Abe Lincoln and old political cartoons. We were seated at our table with some delicious rolls and veggies with ranch dressing. K instantly knew what he wanted: the Legendary Mutton Chop, rare. And he convinced E to order the more expensive Dover Sole as well. E also got a lemon ginger cocktail, which K actually enjoyed (and couldn’t even feel the alchohol in!).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/g9RfZUO9S6OWhKLRv78srw?viewBox=703%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/JnVw2KEQTp2QAT9-Hn6GXA?viewBox=1249%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Expecting a regular-sized cut of lamb for $60 at a famous restaurant like Keen’s, K was absolutely bewildered when this giant piece of meat was placed in front of him.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/qa9wnTALTOafQDW6ApaE3Q?viewBox=703%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Frantically searching through the Yelp reviews, we discovered that most people suggested the dish to be shared by two! Alas, E could not be of any help, yet K confidently announced, “I will do it!” The first bite into the mutton chop was like heaven, and K wanted to cry. The meat soaked in juices was so delicious, and the sweet minty jelly that was served alongside it created a refreshing contrast in flavor, texture, and temperature that ensured the dish never got boring, even nearly two hours later as K definitely showed signs of overburden. The previously consumed rolls and veggies became deep regrets, although the bok choy-like greens were still too good to pass up. E watched with great interest as K slowly traded his sanity and stomach capacity for more bloody goodness, as she had long ago finished her tasty, and reasonably-sized, fish and potatoes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/Y-qGl79bQJ-m7-vdLYU2_w?viewBox=1249%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But finally, with much aplomb, K succeeded in eating two adults’ worth of mutton chop!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/KYlIjsLoSfqCnMFhFEyQ3g?viewBox=703%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In complete disbelief, we somehow arrived at the crazy decision to still order creme brulee for dessert. It came out with a candle for K’s birthday, and K wished to not vomit later ( among other things). K had two bites and wisely left the rest for E. Stuffed and loopy, we walked off our dinner at Bryant Park, where there was a winter village and ice rink set up. E + K reminised and watched people struggle as the staff showed off in front of them. Finally, feeling surprisingly not that bad (the wish worked!), we went home to share our pics and laughter with friends and family. Just another increment in age, but a night and meal to remember :)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://thumbnails-photos.amazon.com/v1/thumbnail/xr2bk-xWRi6jXIKrNKiFIg?viewBox=703%2C937&amp;amp;ownerId=A162HQHSXNNQIH&amp;amp;groupShareToken=utZYY3mwTpGX7bOjEzZGtw.gC8ZExI67DaZhaH_9bzTAd&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Esha Wang</name></author><category term="life" /><summary type="html">January 13, 2022</summary></entry></feed>